<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jimmy Hong</title>
    <link>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jimmy Hong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:04:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jimmyhong23.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/posts/my-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:04:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/posts/my-projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my current projects below!
Website using Hugo!
Hugo website currently works with CF, but no direct link as I have this website. Files with CF implementation is on my GitHubhere.
Website using Verse!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:56:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hiyo!
I am currently a 20 year old, who is attending school at University at Buffalo. On top of my academics, I&amp;rsquo;m currently an intern at the leading cloud foundry consultancy company - Stark &amp;amp; Wayne.
I am expected to graduate in 2020 with a B.S in Computer Science. I am just enjoying the ride and am using Hugo to create my website!
Some of my hobbies include: hiking, climbing, going to the gym and when I have spare time, I play League of Legends!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/portfolio/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/portfolio/website/</guid>
      <description>This is a personal project of mine as I think it is good for all potential Computer Science graduates to have a website. This allows recruiters to see what you are capable of, and it is good to keep track of all your things!
Currently, I have it hosted on GCP (Google Cloud Platform) but I have also implemented Cloud Foundry using PWS into my website that can be seen on my GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Webscraper</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/portfolio/webscraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jimmyhong23.com/portfolio/webscraper/</guid>
      <description>While interning at Stark &amp;amp; Wayne, I&amp;rsquo;ve created a Python script that would scrape data during an event based off a website called &amp;ldquo;Sched&amp;rdquo;. After the data was scraped, the results were on a csv file. This was built using BeautifulSoup and Requests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>